<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BeingCitizen</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">592225087609515</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="openDrawer">open</string>
    <string name="closeDrawer">close</string>
    <string name="debate"> ------ x ------\nContent\n------ x ------
    </string>
    <string name="hash"> Content </string>
    <string name="title">My Description</string>
    <string name="context_menu">Context menu</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Polls</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Blogs</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Cartoons</string>
    <string name="terms">BeingCitizen in all its technology, aims to be a curated hyperlocal social media network. Our services aim to connect citizens with the relevant stakeholders from the point of view of delivering
Governance i.e. State legislators, executive, other government bodies as well as relevant citizens lying within the relevant governance boundaries at the Constituency/State/Country level.\nThis Privacy Policy (further referred to as ‘Policy’) lays down rules for how and when BeingCitizen
uses and shares the information when you use the services on the Network between the various
stakeholders i.e. Citizens, Government and Corporate Sector alike. We, at BeingCitizen respect your
privacy and appreciate the sensitivity of all matters that will subsequently be put out in public
domain and possibly scrutinized further outside the ambit of the Platform itself. Therefore, the
minimum data collected across a user’s activity on the platform to further improve the user
experience on the platform of BeingCitizen itself.\nHenceforth, this Policy document aims to list down feature-wise Privacy intention from the point of
view of Users.\n\nCampaigns: Campaigns become the action centres on the BeingCitizen Platform that brings
together the Government apparatus to the Citizens. More so, to balance the equation and add
credibility to the platform, the identity of the creator of the Campaign and its followers becomes
relevant even for his corresponding MLA to address the desired change and therefore visible to all
users.\n\nThe ‘Community’: These, as a feature, necessitate opinion and for that reason, the identity of the
users using the feature thereby is discoverable by all users to the platform alike. The information as
gathered from these platforms can be discovered either by rendering to other users upon their use
of the platform or could otherwise be discoverable through the user profiles. The data as generated
can the stored by the website and could be used offline to analyse the relevant opinion from the use
of the hash tags as provided and used.\n\nBlogs, Debates &amp; Cartoons: These elements are discoverable and promote user engagement
within the BeingCitizen platform.\n\nPolls: Polls instigate user opinion over any kind of a broad theme that the platform does support.
This can range to a host of topics that might be ranging to a sponsored interest to an opinion poll.</string>
    <string name="login">By Creating An Account, You Agree To Being Citizen\'s Terms Of Services. Privacy Policy. Cookie Policy &amp; Content Policies</string>
    <string name="message_founder">“One person can make a difference and everyone should try."\n- John F Kennedy</string>
    <string name="message_help">BeingCitizen is a citizen centred approach to drive social change. It brings the everyday citizens on a  common digital platform to their elected leaders whom they have duly elected by crowd-sourcing the  popular opinion of the citizens that could be further presented to these elected representatives who  are also, by the virtue of their position, the change enablers within their constituencies. This goes  hand in hand with the objective of cultivating honest political opinion on the platform that goes on  to breed social consciousness for everyone across the platform through the community elements  that promote coming through of sound opinion with the best possible curation of content.\n\nBeingCitizen is a bold initiative. For all its boldness, it would be the most advisable for all users to use  the best of their discretion while posting anything. ‘Campaigns’ as an element allow you to raise  your voice (and solutions) about the most pertinent and local issues that you might face in your  constituency of work, residence, and through the shareability elements allow you to broadcast your  voice to the relevant audience who would feel equally strongly about them too. While other  elements of ‘Debates’, ‘Polls’ and ‘Community’ solicit your views on a host of topics such as National  Politics, Economics, state of the nation, while curating the content from a central point. In all this, it  might be stated that there will be zero tolerance towards rhetoric and hate speech that could be  stemming from one’s adverse beliefs.\n\nBeingCitizen in its vision; seeks to be action-oriented and eventually value additive to all its users  through the chosen path of social change. With that vision, we aim to answer the larger question by  doing the small things right. So hop along, for this initiative is nothing with you, for we are here to  restore your very expectations in the forgotten system and, for the fact that this revolution has only  just begun.
    </string>
    <string name="shikhar">-Shikhar Madan</string>
    <string name="contact_us">We are a bunch of idealists who are in the mind-frame to challenge the status-quo of the system we  are a part of. We are strongly inclined to be unbiased in our actions and hope the same could be  extrapolated to fellow citizens as well. If you think you have a proposal for us, we are willing to  listen. Also, if you think you could add value to our team by fitting in the requirements as mentioned  above, more the reason for you to announce yourself to us.\n\n\n\nContact: Mail at shikhar@beingcitizen.com or Call at +91 9650 101 508\n\n\n\nWe will get back to you, Citizen.</string>
</resources>
